A Preliminary Inventory of the Deaver & Hannaford, Inc. Records, 1960-2008
Hoover Institution Archives
Deaver & Hannaford, Inc. Records,
1960-2008
76122
Deaver & Hannaford, Inc.
99 manuscript boxes, 1 card file box (41.2 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Correspondence, memoranda, reports, schedules, public opinion polling data, promotional material, press releases, news summaries, and clippings, relating to the political career of Ronald Reagan, the 1976 and 1980 Reagan presidential campaigns, and speaking and writing projects of Ronald and Nancy Reagan.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Materials were acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1976
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog Socrates at http://library.stanford.edu/webcat. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in Socrates is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Biography Note
American public relations firm, based in Los Angeles
Scope and Content of Collection
Correspondence, memoranda, reports, schedules, public opinion polling data, promotional material, press releases, news summaries, and clippings, relating to the political career of Ronald Reagan, the 1976 and 1980 Reagan presidential campaigns, and speaking and writing projects of Ronald and Nancy Reagan
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in Stanford University's online catalog.
Subjects
Reagan, Nancy, 1923-; Reagan, Ronald.; Presidents--United States--Election--1976.; Presidents--United States--Election--1980.; California--Politics and government--1951-; Deaver, Michael K.; Hannaford, Peter.
Container List
- Ronald Reagan general file, 1966-1980 (Box 1)
  - Alumni, 1974-1975 (Folder 1: 1)
  - Book projects
    - Adler et al; contracts and correspondence, 1977-1979 (Folder 1: 2)
    - Manuscript--Nancy Reagan, 1979. (Folder 1: 3-4)
      Includes correspondence and memoranda
    - Manuscript--Ronald Reagan, 1977-1981. (Folder 1: 5)
      Includes correspondence, memoranda, and publishing agreement
    - Pre-1966 correspondence, memoranda, and clippings, 1960-1975.; See also box 10 (Folder 1: 6)
      Includes correspondence with Hugh Hefner and Art Linkletter and also some from later years.
  - Budgets and programs, 1974-1977 (Folder 1: 7)
  - California record, 1967-1979 (Folder 1: 8)
  - Campaign committees, 1979 (Folder 1: 9)
  - Clippings, 1978-1979. (Folder 1: 10-11)
    Includes campaign clippings
  - Film project, 1978 (Box-folder 2: 1)
  - Gubernatorial accomplishments, 1967-1975 (Folder 2: 2)
  - Hoover Institution annual reports, 1977-1978 (Folder 2: 3)
  - LP record album "Ronald Reagan: The Great Moments," drafts, proofs, transcripts, memos, and correspondence, 1977-1978 (Folder 2: 4-5)
    Includes related materials
  - Meetings (Senate and House, 1979 January 24) (Folder 2: 6)
  - Memoranda, including related materials, to Governor Ronald Reagan from
    - Deaver & Hannaford
      - 1978 (Folder 2: 7)
      - 1979 (Folder 2: 8)
      - 1977 (Box-folder 3: 1)
      - 1976 (Folder 3: 2)
    - Allen, Richard, 1978-1979 (Folder 3: 3)
    - Anderson, Martin, 1978-1979 (Folder 3: 4)
    - Gavin, William, 1978-1979 (Folder 3: 5)
    - Hyde, Murray, 1978 (Folder 3: 6)
    - Khachigian, Ken, 1979 (Folder 3: 7)
    - McClaughry, John, 1979 (Folder 3: 8)
    - Whalen, Richard, 1978-1979 (Folder 3: 9)
    - Zycher, Ben, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 4: 1)
  - Pepperdine University, 1974-1975 (Folder 4: 2)
  - Position papers
    - 1980 (Folder 4: 3-4)
    - 1979 (Folder 4: 5)
    - SALT II, 1979 (Folder 4: 6)
  - Record project (Garabedian), 1977. (Folder 4: 7)
    Includes memoranda and contract for LP records of Ronald Reagan's radio broadcasts
  - "The Reagan Record, 1967-1974," 1979 November, a compilation of Ronald Reagan's accomplishments based on contemporaneous and retroactive newspaper and magazine articles, political biographies, press releases, and speeches of Governor Ronald Reagan and other administration officials (Folder 4: 8)
  - S P (signed personally?) letters, 1978-1979. (Folder 4: 9-10)
    Includes list of correspondents and The Evolution of Soviet Security Strategy, 1965-1975, Avigdor Haselkorn, 1978
  - Smith, William French, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 5: 1)
  - Surrogate book, 1979 (Folder 5: 2)
  - Task forces, 1975 (Folder 5: 3)
  - Travel
    - General. Financial records, 1974-1975 (Folder 5: 4)
    - England and Europe, 1978 (Folder 5: 5-6)
    - Europe, 1978 (Folder 5: 7)
    - Foreign, 1967-1974 (Folder 5: 8)
    - Japan, 1978 (Folder 5: 9)
    - Latin America, 1979 (Folder 5: 10)
    - Mexico/Canada, 1979 (Folder 5: 11)
    - Mideast/USSR, 1979 (Folder 5: 12)
    - Orient and Iran, 1978 (Folder 5: 13)
  - Vital Speeches of the Day, 1978 May and July (Folder 5: 14)
- Reagan for President Committee file, 1975-1980 (Box 6)
  - Advertising
    - General, 1975-1980 (Folder 6: 1-4)
    - C. Z. Wick film, 1979 (Folder 6: 5)
  - Advisory committees, 1980 (Folder 6: 6)
  - Age issue, undated (Folder 6: 7)
  - Agreements, undated (Folder 6: 8)
  - Ballots for general election, 1980 (Folder 6: 9)
  - Candidates
    - John Connally, 1979-1980 (Folder 6: 10)
    - Philip Crane, 1979 (Folder 6: 11)
  - Client, 1979 March (Folder 6: 12)
  - Clippings, 1979-1980 (Folder 6: 13)
  - Convention (Box 7)
    - General, 1980 (Folder 7: 1-3)
    - Congratulatory letters and wires, 1980 (Folder 7: 4)
    - Delegates, 1980 (Folder 7: 5)
    - First name card file copies, 1980 (Folder 7: 6)
  - Inauguration, 1980 (Folder 7: 7)
  - Lease for office space, 1978-1979 (Folder 7: 8)
  - Speech file, 1979, and announcement, 1979 November 13 (Folder 7: 9-10)
  - Newsletter, 1979 (Box-folder 8: 1)
  - Personnel, 1979 (Folder 8: 2)
  - Primaries, 1980 (Folder 8: 3)
  - Primary ballot filing, 1980 (Folder 8: 4)
  - Releases, 1979-1980 (Folder 8: 5)
  - Resumes, 1978-1980 (Folder 8: 6)
  - Sample ballots, 1980 (Folder 8: 7-9)
  - Secret Service--Nancy Reagan, 1980 (Folder 8: 10)
  - Schedules for transition, 1980 (Folder 8: 11-13)
- Ronald Reagan speech file, 1980 (Box 9)
  - "Shining City on a Hill," speech, American Society of Newspaper Editors, 1980 April 8. (Folder 9: 1)
    Typescript
  - "Leadership and Presidency," speech, CBS Radio Network, 1980 July.; See also box 12 (Folder 9: 2)
    Typescript. Includes press release.
  - Acceptance speech, GOP Convention, Detroit, Michigan, 1980 July 17.; See also box 12 (Folder 9: 3)
    Typescript and printed copy. Includes correspondence and memoranda.
  - Speech, Urban League, New York, 1980 August 5. (Folder 9: 4)
  - "Peace: Restoring the Margin of Safety," speech, Veterans of Foreign Wars Convention, Chicago, Illinois, 1980 August 18. (Folder 9: 5)
    Holograph and typescript
  - "Strength," speech, American Legion, Boston, Massachusetts, 1980 August 20. (Folder 9: 6)
  - Speech, Labor Day, Jersey City, New Jersey, 1980 September 1. (Folder 9: 7)
    Typescript. Includes memoranda
  - Speech, B'nai B'rith Forum, Washington, D.C., 1980 September 3. (Folder 9: 8)
- Press releases, 1977-1979 (Folder 9: 9)
- Press releases and speeches, 1973-1975 (Folder 9: 10)
- Announcement signed by March Fong-Eu certifying Ronald Reagan's selection as the presidential nominee of the Republican Party, Sacramento, California, 1980 July 15 (Box-folder 10: 1)
- Correspondence, 1960-1980
  - Unidentified, 1978 (Folder 10: 2)
  - Undated, letter from Ronald Reagan in support of A Hard Look at the New Cuba, a television/film program (Folder 10: 3)
  - Beilenson, Laurence W., 1977 (Folder 10: 4)
  - Cooke, Robin, 1979 (Folder 10: 5)
  - Federal Election Commission, 1977 (Folder 10: 6)
  - Hannaford, Peter, 1980 (Folder 10: 7)
  - Harkins, Jerry Jr., Mrs., 1962 (Folder 10: 8)
  - Harvey, Mose L., undated (Folder 10: 9)
  - Kirkpatrick, Jeane J., undated (Folder 10: 10)
  - Laxalt, Paul, 1979 (Folder 10: 11)
  - Nicolaides, Philip, 1979 (Folder 10: 12)
  - Playboy, 1960.; See also box 1 (Folder 10: 13)
  - Shaw, Edward S., 1978 (Folder 10: 14)
  - Wilson, Robert G., 1978 (Folder 10: 15)
- Information about family, films, first term as governor, private life at the ranches, 1976 campaign; memorandum from Peter Hannaford to Nancy Reagan re book questionnaire; and memorandum re Good Housekeeping photographs, 1979? (Folder 10: 16)
- Memorandum from Peter Hannaford to Ronald Reagan re radio taping, 1976 November 23 (Folder 10: 17)
- Memoranda to Governor Ronald Reagan and Nancy Reagan.
  Includes handwritten comments by Ronald Reagan
  - Peter Hannaford to Nancy Reagan, 1977 November 16, re book contract (Folder 10: 18)
  - Peter Hannaford to Governor Ronald Reagan, 1978 May 24 and August 2; and 1980 May 27 (Folder 10: 19)
  - Richard B. Wirthlin to Governor Ronald Reagan, 1979 July 19 (Folder 10: 20)
- Notes by Ronald Reagan, undated (Folder 10: 21)
- Reel-to-reel audiotape from the 1966 gubernatorial campaign, 1984 (Folder 10: 22)
- Social Security alternative, undated (Folder 10: 23)
- Correspondence, 1977-1980 (Box 11)
  - With Michael Deaver
    - General - B-W, 1977-1980 (Folder 11: 1)
    - Baker, Howard, 1980 (Folder 11: 2)
    - Baker, James A., III, 1977 (Folder 11: 3)
    - Carter, Jimmy, 1977 (Folder 11: 4)
    - Laxalt, Paul, 1979 (Folder 11: 5)
    - Sparkman, John, 1977 (Folder 11: 6)
    - Weinberger, Caspar W., 1979 (Folder 11: 7)
  - With Peter Hannaford
    - General - A-W, 1977-1980 (Folder 11: 8)
    - Baker, Howard, 1977 (Folder 11: 9)
    - Gergen, David, 1980 (Folder 11: 10)
    - Hatch, Orin G., 1977 (Folder 11: 11)
    - Howe, Derek A., 1979-1980 (Folder 11: 12)
    - Ikle, Fred C., 1978-1979 (Folder 11: 13)
    - Laxalt, Paul, 1979 (Folder 11: 14)
    - Meese, Edwin, III, 1980 (Folder 11: 15)
    - Reagan, Nancy, 1980 (Folder 11: 16)
    - Schlesinger, James R., 1978-1979 (Folder 11: 17)
- Foreword to Rebirth of a Nation, 1977 October 6. (Folder 11: 18)
  Typescript. Includes related materials
- Memoranda from Peter Hannaford to Martin Anderson, Edwin Meese, Ronald Reagan, and others, 1979-1980 (Folder 11: 19)
- Ronald Reagan photographs, 1982 (Folder 11: 20)
- Speeches by Ronald Reagan, 1979
  - "World Challenges, 1979," address, Pepperdine University, Malibu, California, 1979 January 12. (Folder 11: 21)
  - "SALT and the Search for Peace," excerpts from remarks, Republican State Central Committee of California Convention, San Diego, California, 1979 September 15. (Folder 11: 22)
  - Speech, Republican Nomination for President of the United States, New York, 1979 November 13. (Folder 11: 23)
- Woloshyn, George, 1979 (Folder 11: 24)
- Assignments and projects of the research and writing unit 1980 GOP convention (Box-folder 12: 1)
- Letter from Peter Hannaford to Molly Tuthill, 1984 (Folder 12: 2)
- List of foreign and defense policy experts, 1979 (Folder 12: 3)
- Memoranda, 1978-1980
  - China, 1978 March 8 (Folder 12: 4)
  - On appointments, 1980 November 15 (Folder 12: 5)
- Notes from a telephone conversation between Peter Hannaford and Alan Greenspan, undated (Folder 12: 6)
- Speeches, 1960-1980
  - "Encroaching Central," speech, 1960. (Folder 12: 7)
    Typescript. Includes correspondence between Peter Hannaford, Richard Nixon, Harry O'Connor, and Ronald Reagan, 1975
  - Speech, American Society of Newspaper Editors, Washington, D.C., 1980 April 8. (Folder 12: 8)
  - Speech, evening of primary, Los Angeles, California, 1980 June 3. (Folder 12: 9)
  - Acceptance speech, drafted by George Gilder, 1980 July. (Folder 12: 10)
    Typescript. Includes an issue of Imprimis, 1980 December
  - "Leadership and the Presidency," speech, CBS Radio Network, 1980 July 4.; See also box 9 (Folder 12: 11)
    Typescript.
  - Statement on automobile industry, 1980 July 13. (Folder 12: 12)
  - Talking points for delegate reception, GOP convention, Detroit, Michigan, 1980 July 14. (Folder 12: 13)
  - "Non-intervention," speech, 1980 July 15. (Folder 12: 14)
  - Speech, Ford as vice president, 1980 July 16. (Folder 12: 15)
  - Acceptance speech, nomination for the presidency of the United States, Detroit, Michigan, 1980 July 17.; See also box 9 (Folder 12: 16-17)
  - "Friends," lead-in to Ronald Reagan speech, ministers in Dallas, Texas, 1980 August 22. (Folder 12: 18)
  - Speech, 1980 November 3. (Folder 12: 19)
- "California in the Reagan Years: Trends in the Economy and Public Service," Richard W. Gable, 1979 February. (Box-folder 13: 1)
- Correspondence, 1977-1980. (Folder 13: 2)
  Includes memoranda, reprints of a television interview and radio program, and some of Ronald Reagan's speeches and statements
- Correspondence, 1977. (Folder 13: 3)
  Includes letters from Peter Hannaford to Jesse Helms and from Ronald Reagan to William D. Crandall
- Government officials' address list, 1974 (Folder 13: 4)
- Office file, Hannaford Company, Inc., 1979 (Folder 13: 5)
- Press clippings, 1976 (Folder 13: 6)
- Reagan for President Committee, 1979 (Folder 13: 7)
- Reprints of different radio programs, editorials, and newspaper columns Select Committee, 1979 (Folder 13: 8-9)
- "Controlling Crime in California," report of the Governor's, 1973 August (Box-folder 14: 1)
- Statements by Ronald Reagan on various subjects, such as abortion, agriculture, civil rights, Cuba, Cyprus, insurance, labor, law enforcement, USSR, and Vietnam, 1978 (Folder 14: 2)
- Welfare reform materials, 1974 December (Folder 14: 3)
- Office file of Governor Ronald Reagan, 1968-1980 (Box-folder 15: 1)
  - "Californians for Lower Taxes," memorandum to all county chairmen, 1973 September 20; "Consumer Price Index," 1974 February; and "Governor's Survey on Efficiency and Cost Control–-Summary Report and Recommendations,", 1968 February
  - "Ronald Reagan Speaks Out on the Issues,", 1980 (Folder 15: 2)
  - State of the State Address, 1974 January 9, and Reagan and Bush campaign materials, 1980 (Folder 15: 3-4)
- Carter vs. Reagan's stand on various issues, 1976 (Box-folder 16: 1)
- Political, 1973, Book I. (Folder 16: 2)
  See also box 17
- Printed matter on various issues, 1976 (Folder 16: 3)
- Political, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 17: 1-2)
- Political, 1973, Book II., See also box 16 (Folder 17: 3)
- Agriculture and Services (A and S), 1971-1977 (Box 18)
  - Agency, 1975-1977 (Folder 18: 1)
  - Agriculture, 1975-1977 (Folder 18: 2)
  - Agricultural unions, 1971-1977 (Folder 18: 3-5)
  - State employees, 1975-1977 (Folder 18: 6)
- Arts, 1975-1976.; See also box 24 (Folder 18: 7)
- Brown, Jerry. General, 1974-1977 (Folder 18: 8-9)
- Business and Transportation (B and T), 1975-1977
  - Agency, 1975-1977 (Folder 18: 10)
  - Business climate, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 19: 1)
  - Transportation, 1975-1977 (Folder 19: 2)
- Campaign--Jerry Brown, 1976 (Folder 19: 3-4)
- Education, 1975-1977
  - General, 1975 (Folder 19: 5)
  - Finance, 1976-1977 (Folder 19: 6)
  - K-12, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 20: 1)
  - University of California, 1975-1977 (Folder 20: 2-3)
  - Executive appointments, 1975-1976.; See also box 25 (Folder 20: 4-5)
  - Finance (clippings), 1975-1977 (Box-folder 21)
  - Budget, 1975-1977 (Folder 21: 1)
  - Taxes, 1975-1977 (Folder 21: 2-3)
- Health and Welfare, 1975-1977
  - Corrections, 1975-1977 (Folder 21: 4-5)
  - Health (clippings and printed matter), 1976-1977 (Folder 21: 6-7)
  - Reports (Box 22)
    - "A Management Review of the California Community Mental Health System," Office of the Auditor General, 1975 February (Folder 22: 1)
    - "A Study of the Administration of State Health Programs," State of California, 1976 January (Folder 22: 2)
  - Medi-Cal, 1975-1977 (Folder 22: 3)
  - Welfare, 1975-1977 (Folder 22: 4)
- Legal Affairs, 1976-1977
  - Capital punishment, 1976-1977 (Folder 22: 5)
  - Legislature, 1975-1977 (Folder 22: 6)
- Press/Media (clippings), 1975-1976 (Box-folder 23: 1)
- Resources, 1975-1977.; See also box 28 and 29
  - Coast, 1975-1977 (Folder 23: 2)
  - Energy, 1975-1977 (Folder 23: 3)
  - Forestry, 1975-1977 (Folder 23: 4)
  - Land use, 1975-1977 (Folder 23: 5)
  - Parks and recreation, 1975-1977 (Folder 23: 6)
  - Redwood Park, 1976-1977 (Folder 23: 7)
  - Water, 1976-1977 (Folder 23: 8-9)
- Agriculture and Services (A and S), 1975-1979 (Box 24)
  - Agency, 1975-1979 (Folder 24: 1)
  - Agriculture, 1977-1979 (Folder 24: 2)
  - Agricultural unions, 1977-1979 (Folder 24: 3)
  - Consumer affairs, 1975-1978 (Folder 24: 4)
  - Industrial relations (CAL OSHA), 1975-1978 (Folder 24: 5)
  - State employees, 1977-1979 (Folder 24: 6)
- Arts, 1978.; See also box 18 (Folder 24: 7)
- Brown, Jerry, 1966-1980
  - General, 1977-1979 (Folder 24: 8-9)
  - Economy in government and philosophy of government (clippings), 1975-1978 (Folder 24: 10)
  - Remarks, Edmund G., Sr., on election of 1966, 1977-1980 (Folder 24: 11)
- Business and Transportation (B and T), 1975-1981
  - Agency, 1978-1979 (Folder 24: 12)
  - Bridges: Southern crossing, 1975 (Folder 24: 13)
  - Business climate, 1977-1980 (Folder 24: 14-15)
  - California Highway Patrol (CHP), 1975 (Folder 24: 16)
  - Housing, 1975-1978. (Folder 24: 17)
    Includes a report, "An Urban Strategy for California," 1978
  - Insurance, 1975-1978 (Folder 24: 18)
  - Transportation, 1977-1981 (Folder 24: 19)
- Campaign 1978, 1976-1978 (Folder 24: 20)
- Campaign 1980, 1977-1978 (Folder 24: 21)
- Community relations, 1975-1979 (Folder 24: 22)
- Cory, Kenneth, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 25: 1)
- Dymally, Mervyn (lieutenant governor), 1975-1977 (Folder 25: 2)
- Education, 1975-1980
  - General, 1977-1980 (Folder 25: 3)
  - Busing, 1975-1979 (Folder 25: 4)
  - California State University Campus (CSUC), 1975-1980 (Folder 25: 5)
  - Community colleges, 1975-1977 (Folder 25: 6)
  - Ethnic studies, 1975 (Folder 25: 7)
  - Finance, 1977-1980 (Folder 25: 8)
  - Higher—Faculty
    - General, 1976-1978 (Folder 25: 9)
    - Eldridge Cleaver, 1975-1977 (Folder 25: 10)
  - K-12, 1977-1979 (Folder 25: 11)
  - Student aid, 1975-1977 (Folder 25: 12)
  - Students, Communication with, 1975-1978 (Folder 25: 13)
  - Tenure, 1975 (Folder 25: 14)
  - University of California, 1977-1980 (Folder 25: 15)
- Executive, 1975-1980.; See also box 20
  - General, 1975-1980 (Folder 25: 16)
  - Appointments, 1978-1980 (Folder 25: 17)
    - General
      - General
        - 1979 February-December (Box-folder 26: 1)
        - 1980 January-December (Folder 26: 2)
  - Jet, 1975 (Folder 26: 3)
  - Washington office, 1975-1980 (Folder 26: 4)
- Federal–State relations, 1975-1979 (Folder 26: 5)
- Finance, 1975-1981
  - Bonds, 1975 (Folder 26: 6)
  - Budget, 1977-1981
    - General, 1977-1981 (Folder 26: 7)
    - 1979 January-July, and 1981 January (Folder 26: 8)
  - Governor's mansion, 1975-1980 (Folder 26: 9)
  - Proposition 1, 1977-1979 (Folder 26: 10)
  - Taxes, 1977-1979 (Folder 26: 11)
- Health and Welfare, 1975-1981 (Box 27)
  - Agency, 1975-1979 (Folder 27: 1)
  - Corrections, 1977-1980 (Folder 27: 2)
  - Drug abuse, 1975-1978 (Folder 27: 3)
  - Employment, 1975-1979 (Folder 27: 4-5)
  - Food stamps, 1975-1977 (Folder 27: 6)
  - Health, 1977-1980 (Folder 27: 7)
  - Medi-Cal, 1977-1981 (Folder 27: 8-9)
  - Mental health, 1975-1981 (Folder 27: 10)
  - Minimum wage, 1976-1977 (Folder 27: 11)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO), 1975-1979 (Folder 27: 12)
  - Rehabilitation, 1975-1978 (Folder 27: 13)
  - Welfare, 1975-1980 (Box-folder 28: 1)
- Information Services Offices, 1976 (Folder 28: 2)
- Labor, 1975-1979 (Folder 28: 3)
- Legal affairs, 1975-1980
  - Abortion, 1976-1978 (Folder 28: 4)
  - Capital punishment, 1977-1979 (Folder 28: 5)
  - Courts, 1975-1979 (Folder 28: 6)
  - Gun control, 1976-1977 (Folder 28: 7)
  - Law enforcement, 1975-1979 (Folder 28: 8)
  - Military, 1975-1979 (Folder 28: 9)
  - Office of Criminal Justice Planning (OCJP), 1975-1976 (Folder 28: 10)
  - Pardon/Commutation, 1977-1980 (Folder 28: 11)
  - Pornography, 1976-1977 (Folder 28: 12)
  - Radicals, 1976-1980 (Folder 28: 13)
- Legislature, 1977-1979
  - General, 1977-1979 (Folder 28: 14)
  - Reapportionment, 1979 (Folder 28: 15)
- Little Hoover Commission, 1977-1978 (Folder 28: 16)
- Local government, 1975-1978 (Folder 28: 17)
- Press/Media, 1977-1978 (Folder 28: 18)
- Public Utilities Commission (P.U.C.), 1975-1979 (Folder 28: 19)
- Resources, 1975-1980.; See also box 23
  - Air pollution, 1975-1979 (Folder 28: 20)
  - Agency, 1975-1979 (Folder 28: 21)
  - Coast, 1977-1980 (Folder 28: 22)
  - Energy, 1977-1980 (Folder 28: 23)
  - Environment, 1975-1979 (Folder 28: 24)
  - Fish and game, 1975-1979 (Folder 28: 25)
  - Forestry, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 29: 1)
  - Land use, 1978 (Folder 29: 2)
  - Parks and recreation, 1977-1979 (Folder 29: 3)
  - Redwood park, 1977-1978 (Folder 29: 4)
  - Tahoe, 1975-1980 (Folder 29: 5)
  - Water, 1977-1980 (Folder 29: 6)
  - Water pollution, 1975 (Folder 29: 7)
- Space program--California, 1977-1978 (Folder 29: 8)
- State of the State Address, 1974 January 7. (Folder 29: 9)
  Includes related materials, 1976-1978
- Women, 1975-1978 (Folder 29: 10)
- Press clippings for Deaver & Hannaford (Box-folder 30: 1-12)
  - 1974-1975
  - 1976-1980 (Folder 30: 13)
  - 1975 (Box-folder 31: 1-7)
    - January 8-31
    - January 23 - February 22 (Box-folder 32: 1-7)
    - February 23 - March 22 (Box-folder 33: 1-7)
    - March 16 - April 22 (Box-folder 34: 1-11)
    - April 23 - May 22 (Box-folder 35: 1-9)
    - May 16 - June 22 (Box-folder 36: 1-13)
    - June 16 - July 15 (Box-folder 37: 1-8)
    - July 16 - August 15 (Box-folder 38: 1-11)
    - August (Box 39)
      - 8-15 (Folder 39: 1-2)
      - 16-22 (Folder 39: 3-5)
      - 23-31 (Folder 39: 6-9)
    - September
      - 1-7 (Folder 39: 10-12)
      - 8-15 (Box-folder 40: 1-5)
      - 16-22 (Folder 40: 6-10)
      - 23-30 (Folder 40: 11-13)
      - 23-30 (Box-folder 41: 1)
    - October
      - 1-7 (Folder 41: 2-5)
      - 8-15 (Folder 41: 6-9)
      - 16-22 (Folder 41: 10)
      - 16-22 (Box-folder 42: 1-4)
      - 23-31 (Folder 42: 5-9)
    - November
      - 1-7 (Folder 42: 10-11)
      - 1-7 (Box-folder 43: 1-4)
      - 8-15 (Folder 43: 5-8)
      - 8-15 (Box-folder 44: 1)
      - 16-22 (Folder 44: 2-5)
      - 16-22 (Box-folder 45: 1-5)
      - 23-30 (Folder 45: 6-8)
      - 23-30 (Box-folder 46: 1-4)
    - December
      - 1-7 (Folder 46: 5)
      - 8-15 (Folder 46: 6-7)
      - 16-22 (Folder 46: 8)
      - 16-22 (Box-folder 47: 1)
      - 23-31 (Folder 47: 2-3)
  - 1976
    - January
      - 1-7 (Folder 47: 4-5)
      - 8-15 (Folder 47: 6)
      - 8-15 (Box-folder 48: 1-2)
      - 16-22 (Folder 48: 3-5)
      - 23-31 (Box-folder 49: 1-3)
    - February
      - 1-7 (Folder 49: 4-6)
      - 8-15 (Folder 49: 7-8)
      - 8-15 (Box-folder 50: 1)
      - 16-22 (Folder 50: 2-4)
      - 23-29 (Folder 50: 5-9)
      - 23-29 (Box-folder 51: 1)
    - March
      - 1-7 (Folder 51: 2-4)
      - 8-15 (Folder 51: 5-7)
      - 8-15 (Box-folder 52: 1)
      - 16-22 (Folder 52: 2)
      - 23 (Folder 52: 3)
  - 1977
    - April (Folder 52: 4)
    - May
      - 1-7 (Folder 52: 5)
      - 8-15 (Folder 52: 6)
      - 16-22 (Folder 52: 7)
      - 23-31 (Folder 52: 8-9)
    - June
      - 1-7 (Folder 52: 10-12)
      - 8-15 (Folder 52: 13)
      - 8-15 (Box-folder 53: 1-4)
      - 16-22 (Folder 53: 5-6)
      - 23-30 (Folder 53: 7-8)
    - July (Box-folder 54: 1)
- Campaign, 1976
  - July
    - 1-10 (Folder 54: 2)
    - 11-16 (Folder 54: 3)